The princess has returned!
She's in the courtyard with Lady Euphyllia.
Anis!
I don't want to let you become queen.
I don't want to let you give up everything.
So...
Let's settle this.
The Magical Revolution
of the Reincarnated Princess and the Genius Young Lady
You deserve to be rewarded.
I mean, you've been through so much pain!
You could have freedom from now on
and live the way you want!
So there's no need for you to take my place!
Yes, you're right.
There is no replacement for you.
Who could ever hope to take your place?
Miss Anis, I believe in you.
Your dream, your magic,
can fly so much higher and farther.
Your day is yet to come.
When it does, I want to live it with you.
I don't want to sacrifice you
to make my dream come true!
You don't have to go through that for me!
I'm oka—
Don't tell me you're okay!
You're crying right now
because you're not okay at all!
As long as no one's getting hurt, who cares?!
If I give up and just let it happen,
that's where everything ends!
It doesn't matter anymore!
I can't condone anything that hurts you.
I can't forgive a world that hurts you
and tries to crush your dream.
I'll be the only wound you need,
the scar that stops you from giving up.
Even if you resent me or hate me,
I'll keep wishing for your
happiness over and over.
Miss Anis, I want you to be happy.
Happier than anyone in this world.
That goes for me, too.
Aerial Attack: Dragon Heart!
I won't just let you suffer!
That's why I can't let you win!
I don't want to lose!
If this is what it takes to
stop your tears, I won't lose.
I'll accept all of it!
Gather and combine.
Combine... and be!
That's...
It has been done.
Miss Anis!
This is the power within me
that you showed to me!
It's the future you dreamed of!
No matter how many times you try to give up,
I will show it to you!
Arc-en-Ciel!
Miss Anis.
That was... so beautiful.
There's no way I could beat that.
Euphie...
Yes?
You're not fair. You're just not fair!
Miss Anis, it was you
who brought me this far.
I couldn't have made it alone.
I couldn't have loved the world
this much on my own.
The world only looks so beautiful
because you're in it.
If you also think it's beautiful,
then please...
love yourself, too.
Euphie... I... I...
I'm sorry.
I'm not okay.
There's no way I can be okay!
I will hold your hand.
I need you.
You, and no one else.
Anis, I—
Mother...
I'm sorry.
I really don't think I can be queen.
I always knew you condemned yourself
because I can't use magic,
so I thought I should at least take that
off your back by becoming queen...
and that if I didn't, I couldn't call myself
the daughter of you and Father.
I'm sorry for being a useless dau—
How could you call yourself useless?
You're a far better daughter
than I could ever deserve!
Mother...
You've been trying so hard all this time.
But you don't have to try hard
by yourself anymore.
Can I really stay as a princess?
As your and Father's daughter?
Euphie, are you still awake?
Miss Anis?
Oh... S-Sorry to bother you so late.
No, I don't mind at all.
I wanted to say... sorry,
I guess. And thank you.
There's a reason I was so
hung up on being queen,
and being the daughter
of my mother and father.
A reason?
I kept it a secret all this time.
A secret I never shared with anyone.
Anyone? Not even Ilia or Tilty?
Yeah.
You're the first person
I ever thought of telling it to.
I planned to take it with me to my grave.
Euphie...
Will you take this secret
to the grave with me?
Yes. I promise.
I have memories from a past life.
I lived in a completely different world
from this one.
Magic only existed in fairy tales there.
When I saw that magic existed in this world,
I thought it seemed like a dream.
Sometimes I wished it was a dream.
Miss Anis?
Am I really Anisphia Wynn Palettia at all?
On the inside, I'm not simply
"Anisphia Wynn Palettia."
I wondered if my being reborn here
erased the original Anisphia—
if I took their daughter away from them.
When I thought of that... it scared me.
I thought, I must be just a fake...
There's no way you're just a fake!
You're the one who reached out
your hand to me!
The one who pulled me from
the depths of despair that day
was the you who's sitting here now!
It's right here, isn't it?
Everything you felt,
everything you wished for,
everything you wanted... All of it!
The you that you know,
and the you that cares about me,
is undeniably right here.
So please don't call yourself a fake!
To me, you are the greatest
magician in the whole world!
Thank you.
Wh-Why did you kiss me?! You dummy!
Because I wanted to.
W-Wanted to?! You should only
kiss the person you love!
I do love you.
B-But just, like, out of respect
and friendship, right?! It has to be!
If it's what you want, I will offer you
my loyalty and friendship.
But if you can, I'd like you to
accept this feeling for what it is.
Euphie, wait...
I won't wait.
Euphyllia has completed the spirit contract
and been recognized as a member
of the royal family.
The time is right.
I am going to step down.
I entrust you to be the next ruler
of this kingdom, Euphyllia.
Yes, Father.
I accept.
Anis...
You are to support the queen
as her older sister from now on.
Accompany her in forging ahead to the future.
Yes, Father.
My future is with Euphie.
Now, what sort of ruler will you be,
and how will you build up this kingdom?
I will bring a proper end
to the current age of magic
and the traditions we have
kept for generations.
That is my purpose for becoming queen.
And I will build an age in which
magic is accessible to anyone,
not just to the nobility
as their exclusive privilege.
And the one to bring that age will be...
I want...
If I must put it into words,
I want to expand freedom to all.
I see.
I would love to see such a kingdom myself.
I know the two of you can do it.
Still, while it may be freedom,
it's difficult to picture.
A rift separates the way
nobles and commoners think.
Complete understanding
will not come quickly.
Regarding that...
I have a suggestion.
Okay, this is the last delivery.
What? Was there still something else?
Is this...
I requested it.
A magic sword just for you.
Huh?
What is its name?
"Celestial."
It means "of the skies."
Since my Arc-en-Ciel means "rainbow,"
I wanted a name close in meaning.
A rainbow and the sky, huh?
You're right. They do match.
I think it's perfect for the first person
in the world to think about ways to fly.
They're flying!
People other than Miss Anis can fly now!
Everyone, thank you very much
for your generous applause.
Okay, the next thing I have
to show you is... this!
A dress and coat that give anyone
wearing them the ability to fly!
We will now give a demonstration
of flight and aerial dancing.
This is the new shape we wish
to give to this kingdom.
Endless potential, unbound by
established concepts and stereotypes.
That is freedom!
Hey, Euphie...
I'll live a long life, okay?
Please do.
I'll do something about
the immortality, too.
I'll study my hardest.
If nothing else, I could always
become immortal, too.
I look forward to it.
So stay with me forever, okay?
I will.
Together forever.
Euphie...
Let's go!
Yes, Miss Anis!
Fly!
The kingdom's history henceforth
would record the name of the queen
who entrusted the future
to the next generation,
leading it from the old age to the new.
The queen who, in order to
correct warped traditions,
achieved the same great undertaking
as the founding king,
becoming the last noble queen
and the one to end tradition.
That queen's name was
Euphyllia Fez Palettia.
And by the queen's side
was the princess who carried
the original royal family's blood.
An innovator who had been long
persecuted by tradition,
now the leader of the next generation.
The princess who loved
magic more than any other,
despite being shunned by
magic more than any other.
That princess's name was
Anisphia Wynn Palettia.
These two young ladies closed the gap
between tradition and revolution.
The people would relate the legend of their
great accomplishments for years to come.
But all of that is yet to come.
Their revolution, after all,
has only just begun.
Place in the sky...
...a rainbow!
Shower all those...
...who reside in this kingdom...
...with blessings!
Really, Miss Anis! You slept much too late!
Your breakfast will get cold!
Oh... Sorry, Lainie.
Good morning, Miss Anis.
Morning, Euphie.
You don't need to call me "Miss" anymore,
but you still do.
It's a habit.
I'll be more careful from now on, Anis.
Thank you.
You seem to have fully acclimated
to your role as a maid.
It's all thanks to Miss Ilia.
You learn very quickly, Lainie.
You are an apprentice worth teaching.
O-Oh... Not at all...
You have truly been a great help.
Anis?
Nah, it's nothing.
Miss Anisphia, Miss Euphyllia,
you will be late if you don't leave soon.
Huh? It's already that late?!
You take too long to eat, Miss Anis!
Oh, Euphie...
Here.
When will you kiss me
on the lips instead, I wonder?
I-I don't know!
Euphie!
We'll be late, Anis!
Episode Twelve
Their Magical Revolution